SHAWNCONRAD Front-end Web Developer

SEEKING REMOTE ONLY WORK

LOCATION: Austell, GA PHONE: 678-744-3915 EMAIL: shawn@shawnconrad.com WEBSITE: www.shawnconrad.com

PROFILE

Front-end developer with expertise in HTML5, LESS, SCSS, Bootstrap and Material Design. Understanding, knowledge, and tweaking ability of Angular1, JavaScript, and some Angular2 but NOT A PROGRAMMER by any means. Portfolio of work can be viewed at www.shawnconrad.com.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

WEB DEVELOPER - The Home Depot. Atlanta, GA 12/2014 - 06/2016

UI Developer handling all UI components of numerous web applications for The Home Depot. Technology used includes HTML5, CSS3, LESS, Angular v1, jQuery, Bootstrap, Material Design.

WEB DEVELOPER - WebMD. Atlanta, GA 07/2014 - 11/2014

Contracting consultant collaborating with other developers, product managers, designers, and producers to re-skin the WebMD web site while meeting the project's deadlines. Details include developing cross-browser, functional web pages and modules using front-end web languages such as HTML5, CSS3, and jQuery.

UI DEVELOPER - The Coca-Cola Company. Austell GA 11/2013 - 7/2014

Responsible for Freestyle Project to develop E-commerce SAP solution - aka CokeSmart. Designed and developed from wireframes through handing coding in order to revamp several existing B2B website pages. Used HTML5, CSS3, jQuery and JavaScript as needed to provide implementation of B2B applications.

LEAD WEB DEVELOPER - Day Three Media. Kennesaw GA 12/2013 - 5/2014

Lead Web Developer on a team of three. Develop customized responsive websites for mid-level business clients. Hand coding of HTML, CSS, and very light PHP.

WEB DESIGNER - National Builder Supply. Kennesaw GA 5/2013 - 11/2013

Web Designer on a team of eight. Developed design comps and layouts for campaign assets, web banners, blogs, social media features, and display ads. Technology used was Photoshop, HTML, and CSS.

UI WEB DEVELOPER & CEO - Freshco Media. Austell GA 11/2007 - 4/2013

Company owner, UI Developer and Sound Designer consultant.

Sound Designer / Mixer 11/2007-07/2012

- Freelance Sound Designer: TNT, TBS, Cartoon Network: 2010 2012
- Sound Mixer for Tyler Perry's House of Payne and Meet The Browns: 2009

PORTFOLIO: www.shawnconrad.com/#/portfolio

SHAWNCONRAD Front-end Web Developer

SEEKING REMOTE ONLY WORK

- Adjunct teach at School of Audio Engineering Atlanta 2009
- Freelance Sound Designer at Magick Lantern Studio: 2008 2009
- Freelance Sound Mixer for television commercials and reality TV shows: 2007

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Art Institute of Pittsburgh, Online – BS, Web Design & Interactive Media

New York College of Technology, Brooklyn, New York - AAS, Art & Advertising Design

LANGUAGES & SKILLS

HTML5, CSS3, LESS, SCSS, Bootstrap, Material Design, understanding of JavaScript & Angular (but *not* a programmer), Git, Bower, NPM, Agile.

PORTFOLIO: www.shawnconrad.com/#/portfolio